Three AM the cursor blinks alone
새벽 3시 홀로 커서가 깜빡이네
A thousand functions no one's called
천 개의 함수, 불리지 않은
The build keeps failing line by line
빌드는 계속 실패하네 한 줄 한 줄
But I keep writing through the wall
하지만 난 벽을 뚫고 계속 써나가네
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속에서 죽은 코드가 실행되네
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스 묻혀버린 불씨
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드 않고, 아무도 플레이하지 않아
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 켜져 있네
Designed the maps drew every sprite
지도를 설계하고 모든 스프라이트를 그렸지
Scored the music through the night
밤새도록 음악을 작곡했어
The folder grows the version climbs
폴더는 커지고 버전은 올라가네
A finished game that no one finds
아무도 찾지 못하는 완성된 게임
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속에서 죽은 코드가 실행되네
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스 묻혀버린 불씨
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드 않고, 아무도 플레이하지 않아
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 켜져 있네
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속에서 죽은 코드가 실행되네
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스 묻혀버린 불씨
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드 않고, 아무도 플레이하지 않아
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 켜져 있네